Altirra -- Atari 8-bit home computer emulator
Copyright (C) 2008-2025 Avery Lee, All Rights Reserved.

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of  MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.

All trademarks belong to their respective owners. Neither the author nor this program are affiliated with Atari.

Dedicated to The uNK

Special thanks to: Mclane, breaker, Rybags, flashjazzcat, Candle, Drac030, HiassofT, Triads, Vasyl, Fox, JAC!, Sheddy, bf2k+, Kr0tki, xxl, ijor, andym00, Kaz, the Atari800 development team.
